(cheers)
(Audience) Hey! Hey! Hey!
♬～
sp1: (Sanada) ≪For 35 years, I've been living a dull life sp1: I've lived a normal life≫
sp1: >
sp1: ≪While saying that...≫
sp1: ≪But at that time sp1: It came suddenly≫
sp1: ≪Anyone can shine sp1: anytime≫
sp1: ≪Our new path is sp1: Starting now≫
sp1: Full-time employee...
sp1: Good welfare benefits sp1: Saturdays and Sundays off
sp1: Also, if possible, company housing...
sp1: “Up to the second new graduate”
sp1: “Experienced only”
sp1: (sigh)
sp1: “Manpuku Entertainment Production”?
sp1: This is my first time working in the entertainment industry.
sp1: 13 years as a salesperson sp1: Utilizing my work experience
sp1: For the prosperity of your company sp1: I want to do my best.
sp2: (Fukuko) Is that the line that you asked the AI ​​to think about sp2:?
sp1: Huh?
sp2: Hmm, as expected.
sp2: Okay, question.
sp2: What do you want to do at this company?
sp1: Um...
sp1: Of the company's profits... sp2: Not "the company's"
sp2: What you want to do sp2: Dream, dream
sp1: Dream...
sp1: ≪Dream...≫
sp2: Ah...
sp2: Because I don't have anything to say, sp2: To AI... I see.
sp2: thin life
sp2: Is it okay to live like that?
sp1: Me too...
sp1: Really, this is my life...
sp1: But no way...
sp1: I don't think the company will suddenly go bankrupt sp1:
sp1: It can't be helped, can it?
sp2: When you say "I can't help it" sp2:
sp2: Life is over
sp1: If I can change it, sp1: I would like to change it.
sp1: Such a life
sp2: Next person please
sp2: Thank you for your precious time sp2: Thank you for your hard work
sp1: Excuse me
(Asai) Very heavy sp1: (sob)
(Ishida) Weren't you crying just now?
Huh? Is it okay? (Imagawa) I'm more hungry than that.
Hey
Oh, Mr. Yamanaka? Where are you going?
sp3: (Yamanaka) Um...
sp3: Um...
sp3: Lost something sp1: Oh, sorry.
sp3: Don't give up easily
sp3: Anyone can shine anytime
sp1: Huh?
sp3: Ah...
sp3: These are the words my master taught me.
sp1: But me sp1: I'm already a 35 year old man, right?
sp3: I don't believe in such beautiful things either.
sp3: But now...
sp3: I want to believe it.
sp1: Oh sorry
sp3: Are you okay?
sp1: It's okay
sp1: Ah, I have to go now... sp3: Huh?
sp1: I have an interview next.
sp1: Okay then...
sp1: Thank you very much
♬～
(sound of door opening)
sp3: Good morning
sp2: Everyone is here sp3: Yes
sp3: Then again...
sp3: Member and manager sp3: Daisuke Yamanaka
I am Tsuyoshi Imagawa, a former child actor.
Well, I think everyone already knows.
As expected, Ima-chan was a very popular child actor.
I'm Yu Asai, a former J Leaguer.
My name is Naoki Ishida.I was teaching at a junior high school until the other day.
(Kakizaki) Makoto Kakizaki is the host.
sp2: Let's start idol sp2: Eternal Boys with these five people!
Hey! sp3: Please wait a moment
sp2: What? Can you please leave me a pitcher of water?
sp3: Actually, I want to add a 6th person sp2: Huh?
yeah? yeah? yeah? yeah? sp3: Kentaro Sanada 35 years old
sp2: Who is it? (Asai) He seems like a normal person.
Tell me what you're aiming for, manager.
sp3: That's...
♬(In-store music)
Mr. Yamanaka is surprisingly a gambler too.
sp2: “Mo”?
sp2: I don't want to hear that name right now.
(Kakizaki) What is that person so angry about?
sp2: I don't know sp2: Not at all! Really
(cell phone vibration sound)
sp1: Hello...
sp1: Huh! Hiring? (sound of knocking on the wall)
sp1: Oh sorry
sp1: Huh, are you really hired?
sp3: 📱The type of job you want sp3: It might be a little different...
sp3: Do you like idols?
sp1: Idol?
sp1: Ah, sp1: Are you an idol manager?
sp3: Well...
sp3: That's it
sp1: I have no experience, but sp1: Is it okay?
sp3: That's why it's okay sp3: In my office...
sp3: 📱Sanada is required
sp1: By the way, what about company housing?
♬～
sp1: "Eternal Youth"?
sp1: ok
(knock)
(Asai) Please
sp1: Excuse me
(Asai) Huh?
Maybe Mr. Sanada?
sp1: Huh? Why the name...
Hahaha, the real thing is pretty plain too.
sp1: Plain? Sorry
sp1: Ah, from today on, I will be sp1: manager...
(Ishida) Manager? sp3: Are you still changing?
sp3: Hurry... sp1: Ah...
sp3: Sanada, thank you for coming.
sp3: This is Yamanaka, member and manager.
sp1: Are there two managers?
sp3: Ah... well, I'll explain later sp3: Anyway, change into this.
sp1: In the entertainment industry, even managers have sp1: uniforms, right?
sp3: Oh... well, hurry up and change your clothes. sp1: Ah, yes.
(Staff) Coming soon
♬～
sp1: What is that? this clothes
sp1: Just like an idol sp3: Not “like”
sp3: Sanada…
sp3: I'm sorry for deceiving you sp1: I'm deceiving you... Huh?
(Moderator) We will introduce the idol group that will be unveiled today.
Anyone can shine anytime...
sp3: Let's go! sp1: Wait a minute!
(MC) A boy who is around 40 years old but has an eternal heart
This is everyone from the idol group Eternal Boys.
♬～
sp1: What, a dream?
(Asakura) I'm the chef, Nikolai.
sp1: I was like this in my youth sp1: I thought I couldn't do it anymore.
I... I'm scared. What happened all of a sudden?
♬～
What is it? Getting to know each other is getting to know each other.
No matter how hard you try, you can't do it, right?
I hope it gets better from now on!
Let's stop!
sp3: The last sp3 left by the previous president: It was a special project.
sp3: Please lend me your strength.